What are you doing here?!
(Raj:)Maybe Howard and Bernadette said
I could be here!
(Stuart:)Did they?
Answer the question!
What are you doing here?!
(Stuart:)I had nothing else
to do tonight.
(Stuart:)The last couple of months,
(Stuart:)I come here when I
know they're not home.
What?!
(Stuart:)They heard me in
the bushes once,
(Stuart:)but they thought
it was a raccoon.
(Bernadette:)I told you raccoons
don't say "Uh-oh."
(Penny:)You know, one night, Leonard's
nose whistled so loud,
(Penny:)I swear it was like
sleeping on a train track.
(Sheldon:)Have you noticed
it's always an A-flat?
(Bernadette:)Is it?
Oh!
(Penny:)It's like his sinuses
are right here in the car.
(Sheldon:)If we're just going
to drive around aimlessly,
(Sheldon:)the least you could do is
take me for ice cream.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'll take you
for ice cream.
(Sheldon:)Well, see, why can't Amy be
that subservient?
(Sheldon:)She has coitus one time,
suddenly she's Gloria Steinem.
(Sheldon:)Anyway, I suppose an ice cream
parlor will be a good place